<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshop on Computational Models of Natural Argument (CMNA 23)</title>
    <link>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Workshop on Computational Models of Natural Argument (CMNA 23)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dates</title>
      <link>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/dates/</guid>
      <description>Key Dates  Regular Paper submission (long &amp;amp; short papers): 12th May 2023 Review Period: 12th May 2023 &amp;ndash; 2nd June 2023 Notification to authors: 2nd June 2023 Demo &amp;amp; Poster submission (2 page abstract): 2nd June 2023 Final (Camera Ready) version of papers: 23rd June 2023 Workshop: July 9-10th (exact date of workshop within the ICLP schedule to be confirmed)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/home/</guid>
      <description>Since its inception in 2001, the CMNA workshop series has focused upon the issue of modelling “natural” argumentation, where naturalness may range across a variety of forms, perhaps involving the use of visual rather than linguistic means to illustrate a point, for example using graphics or multimedia, or applying more sophisticated rhetorical devices, interacting at various layers of abstraction, or exploiting “extra-rational” characteristics of the audience, taking into account emotions and affective factors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News &amp; Updates</title>
      <link>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organisation</title>
      <link>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/organisation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/organisation/</guid>
      <description>If you have any questions or queries then feel free to contact a member of the organising committee
Organising Committee  Floriana Grasso floriana@liverpool.ac.uk University of Liverpool Nancy Green nlgreen@uncg.edu University of North Carolina Greensboro Jodi Schneider jschneider@pobox.com University of Illinois Urbana Champaign Simon Wells s.wells@napier.ac.uk School of Computing, Edinburgh Napier University  Programme Committee Subject to confirmation&amp;hellip;
 Francielle Alves VargasInstituto de Ciencias Matematicas e de Computacao da Universidade de Sao Paulo (ICMC/USP) Elena CabrioUniversite Cote d&#39;Azur, CNRS, Inria, I3S, France Sylvie DoutreUniversity of Toulouse 1 - IRIT Reva FreedmanNorthern Illinois University Massimiliano GiacominUniversity of Brescia Stella HerasUniversitat Politecnica de Valencia Helmut HoracekSaarland University Mare KoitUniversity of Tartu Collin LynchNorth Carolina State University Elena MusiUniversity of Liverpool Rudi PalmieriUniversity of Liverpool Andrea PazienzaInnovation Lab, Exprivia S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programme</title>
      <link>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/programme/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ll publish a full timetable of events and links to papers CMNA&#39;23 closer to the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submission</title>
      <link>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/submission/</guid>
      <description>Downloadable CFP  Download a PDF version of the first call for papers  Workshop Categories The workshop encourages submissions in four categories:
 Long papers, either reporting on completed work or offering a polemic discussion on a burning issue (up to 10 pages). Short papers describing work in progress (up to 5 pages). Demos (2 page abstract describing the demo) Posters (2 page abstract explaining the concept behind the poster).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Topics</title>
      <link>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/topics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cmna-workshop.github.io/cmna23/topics/</guid>
      <description>The CMNA workshop series focuses on the general issue of modelling &amp;ldquo;natural&amp;rdquo; argumentation.
However, to celebrate our co-location with COMMA, this year we have introduced a special theme on explorations of the relationship between logic programming and computational models of natural argument. Our theme should be interpreted broadly, to reflect the wide range of approaches to recognising, formalising, and understanding the richness of real-world reasoning and communication processes within computational models.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>